

# Gianluigi De Marco

## Contact

**Address** 

Racale, 73055

**Phone** 

0039 3460696468

E-mail

dmgiangi@gmail.com

**WWW** 

https://dmgiangi.dev/

LinkedIn

https://dmgiangi.dev/

## **Framework**

Java & Spring

Very Good

Dart & Flutter

Good

## **Skills**

NoSQL & SQL integration

Very Good

Linux

Very Good

I wrote my first program when I was 6 years old.

Since then I have never abandoned computer science even though I chose a different career path.

in the last few months I have dealt with a study path concerning the backend development in the java-spring environment.

Other skills in web development are the knowledge of the Dart language and the Flutter framework and the use of database systems such as MariaDB and MongoDB

## **Accomplishments**

 Supervised team of 4 staff members in Develhope course.

## **Work History**

2016-09 - Head Pastry Chef

2022-08 Pasticceria Graffio, Galatone

 Trained and mentored team of bakers to maintain product quality and restaurant reputation.

2013-10 - Executive Chef

2016-01 GellGross, Taviano

 Developed menus, controlled food costs and oversaw quality, sanitation and safety processes.

2011-09 - Pastry Chef

Bellissima Ice, Bremen

 Monitored baking ingredient stocks and replenished items to maintain sufficient quantities for pastry production.

## Education

2013-02

2011-09 - High School Diploma

2013-05 I.I.S.S. "FILIPPO BOTTAZZI" - Ugento

2004-09 - High School Diploma

2009-05 I.I.S. "A. Meucci" - Casarano

## **Interests**

Poetry

Hike